A Guide to the Russell Sage Foundation records, Publications FA086
Rockefeller Archive Center
Russell Sage Foundation records, Publications
1908-1975
Rockefeller Archive Center
Russell Sage Foundation
FA086
1.33 Cubic Feet 100 microfilm reels (35mm)
100 Reels 100 microfilm reels (35mm)
Conditions Governing Access
Microfilm open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of the RAC.
Arrangement
Original order, as received.
Scope and Contents
Contains monographs, books, bulletins, papers, reports, and studies produced, or collected, by the Russell Sage Foundation.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred and donated to Rockefeller Archive Center by Russell Sage Foundation in 1999.
- Monographs, Bulletins, and Books Index, 1908-1975; 1; 1.33 Cubic Feet 100 35mm microfilm reels; 100 Reels 100 microfilm reels (35mm)
  - Adams, Thomas Adams - Outline of Town and City Planning, 1935. (Reel 1)
  - Adams, Thomas Adams - Outline of Town and City Planning, 1936. Reprint. (Reel 1)
  - Andrews, F. Emerson - Attitudes towards Giving, 1953 (Reel 1)
  - Andrews, F. Emerson - Corporation Giving, 1952 (Reel 2)
  - Andrews, F. Emerson - Foundations - 20 Viewpoints, 1965. (Reel 2)
  - Andrews, F. Emerson - Legal Instruments of Foundations, 1958. (Reel 2)
  - Andrews, F. Emerson - Philanthropic Foundations, 1956. (Reel 2)
  - Andrews, F. Emerson - Philanthropic Giving, 1950 (Reel 3)
  - Andrews, Frank M. - A Study of Company-Sponsored Foundations, 1960. (Reel 3)
  - Armor, David J. - The American School Counselor, 1969. (Reel 3)
  - Ayres, Leonard P. - Laggards in our Schools, 1909. (Reel 3)
  - Ayres, Leonard P. - An Index Number for State School Systems, 1920. (Reel 3)
  - Astin, Helen S. - The Woman Doctorate in America, 1969 (Reel 3)
  - Ayres, Leonard P. - A Measuring Scale for Ability in Spelling, 1915 (Reel 3)
  - Back, Kurt W. - Beyond Words, 1972 (Reel 3)
  - Baker, Helen Cody and Mary Swain Routzahn - How to Interpret Social Welfare, 1947 (Reel 4)
  - Baker, Helen Cody and Mary Swain Routzahn - How to Interpret Social Work, 1937 (Reel 4)
  - Balbus, Isaac D. - The Dialectics of Legal Repression, 1973 (Reel 4)
  - Balk, Alfred - The Free List, 1971 (Reel 4)
  - Barber, Bernard - Drugs in Society, 1967 (Reel 4)
  - Barber, Bernard et al. - Research on Human Subjects, 1973 (Reel 4)
  - Barnes, Charles B. - The Longshoremen, 1915 (Reel 4)
  - Bell, Wendell and James A. Man (eds.) - The Sociology of the Future, 1971 (Reel 5)
  - Bienen, Henry (ed.) - The Military Intervenes, 1968 (Reel 5)
  - Bloch, Louis - Labor Agreements in Coal Mines, 1931 (Reel 6)
  - Bloom, Samuel W. - The Doctor and his Patient, 1963 (Reel 6)
  - Borgatta, Edgar F., David Fanshel, and Henry J. Meyer - Social Workers' Perceptions of Clients, 1960 (Reel 6)
  - Brackett, Jeffrey R. - The Transportation Problem in American Social Work, 1936. (Reel 6)
  - Breckinridge, Sophonisba P. and Edith Abott - The Delinquent Child and the Home, 1912 (Reel 6)
  - Bridgman, Margaret - Collegiate Education for Nursing, 1953 (Reel 6)
  - Brim, Orville G., Jr. - Education for Child Rearing, 1959 (Reel 7)
  - Brim, Orville G., Jr. - Sociology and the Field of Education, 1958 (Reel 7)
  - Brim, Orville G., Jr. et al. - American Beliefs and Attitudes about Intelligence, 1969, 1959 (Reel 7)
  - Brim, Orville G., Jr. et al. - The Dying Patient, 1970 (Reel 7)
  - Brim, Orville G., Jr. et al. - Experiences and Attitudes of American Adults Concerning Standardized Intelligence Tests, 1965 (Reel 7)
  - Brim, Orville G., Jr. et al. - The Use of Standardized Ability Tests in American Secondary Schools and Their Impact on Students, Teachers, and Administrators, 1965 (Reel 8)
  - Bronfenbrenner, Urie - Two Worlds of Childhood, 1970 (Reel 9)
  - Brown, Esther Lucile - Lawyers and the Promotion of Justice, 1938 (Reel 9)
  - Brown, Esther Lucile - Lawyers, Law Schools, and the Public Service, 1948 (Reel 9)
  - Brown, Esther Lucile - Newer Dimensions of Patient Care (Parts 1-3), 1965 (Reel 9)
  - Brown, Esther Lucile - Nursing as a Profession, 1936 (Reel 9)
  - Brown, Esther Lucile - Nursing as a Profession, Second Edition, 1940, 1949 (Reel 9)
  - Brown, Esther Lucile - Nursing for the Future, 1948 (Reel 10)
  - Brown, Esther Lucile - Physicians and Medical Care, 1937 (Reel 10)
  - Brown, Esther Lucile - The Professional Engineer, 1936 (Reel 10)
  - Brown, Esther Lucile - Social Work as a Profession, 1935 (Reel 10)
  - Brown, Esther Lucile - Social Work as a Profession, 2nd Edition, 1936 (Reel 10)
  - Brown, Esther Lucile - Social Work as a Profession, Third Edition, 1938 (Reel 10)
  - Brown, Esther Lucile - Social Work as a Profession, Fourth Edition, 1942 (Reel 10)
  - Brown, Esther Lucile - The Use of Research by Professional Associations in Determining Program and Policy, 1946 (Reel 10)
  - Brunsman, Howard G. - The Estimation of Population Changesfor New York City, 1955 (Reel 10)
  - Burgess, May Ayres - The Measurement of Silent Reading, 1921 (Reel 10)
  - Burgess, W. Randolph - Trends of School Costs, 1920 (Reel 10)
  - Butler, Elizabeth Beardsley - Saleswomen in Mercantile Stores, 1912 (Reel 10)
  - Campbell, John C. - The Southern Highlander and his Homeland, 1921 (Reel 11)
  - Campbell, Angus and Philip E. Converse (eds.) - The Human Meaning of Social Change, 1972 (Reel 11)
  - Cannon, Ida M. - Social Work in Hospitals, 1913 (Reel 11)
  - Cannon, Ida M. - Social Work in Hospitals, Revised Edition, 1923, 1923 April (Reel 11)
  - Carden, Maren Lockwood - The New Feminist Movement, 1974 (Reel 12)
  - Carlin, Jerome E. - Lawyers' Ethics, 1966 (Reel 12)
  - Caro, Francis G. - Readings in Evaluation Research, 1971 (Reel 12)
  - Cater, Douglass and Stephen Strickland - TV Violence and the Child, 1975 (Reel 12)
  - Chapin, Robert Coit - The Standard of Living among Workingmen's Families in New York City, 1909 (Reel 12)
  - Clausen, John A. - Sociology and the Field of Mental Health, 1956 (Reel 12)
  - Colcord, Joanna C. - Broken Homes, 1919 (Reel 13)
  - Colcord, Joanna C. - Cash Relief, 1936 (Reel 13)
  - Colcord, Joanna C. et al. - Emergency Work Relief, 1932 (Reel 13)
  - Colcord, Joanna C. - Your Community, 1939 (Reel 13)
  - Colcord, Joanna C. - Your Community, Second Edition, 1941, 1941 March (Reel 13)
  - Colcord, Joanna C. - Your Community, Third Edition, 1947, 1947 January (Reel 13)
  - Henderson, Charles Richmond (ed.) - Prison Reform (Vol. I, Correction and Prevention Series), 1910 (Reel 14)
  - Smith, Eugene - Criminal Law in the United States (Vol. I, Correction and Prevention Series), 1910 (Reel 14)
  - Henderson, Charles Richmond (ed.) - Penal and Reformatory Institutions (Vol. II, Correction and Prevention Series), 1910 (Reel 14)
  - Henderson, Charles Richmond - Preventive Agencies and Methods (Vol III, Correction and Prevention Series), 1910. (Reel 14)
  - Hart, Hastings H. - Preventive Treatment of Neglected Children (Vol. IV, Correction and Prevention Series), 1910 (Reel 14)
  - Dahir, James (compiled by) - Community Centers as Living War Memorials, 1946. (Reel 15)
  - Dahir, James (compiled by) - The Neighborhood Unit Plan, 1947 (Reel 15)
  - Deacon, J. Byron - Disasters, 1918 (Reel 15)
  - Devine, Edward T. - Report on the Desirability of Establishing an Employment Bureau in the City of New York, 1909 (Reel 15)
  - Duffy, John - A History of Public Health in New York City, 1625-1866, 1968 (Reel 15)
  - Duffy, John - A History of Public Health in New York City, 1866-1966, 1974 (Reel 16)
  - Duncan, Otis Dudley, Howard Schuman, and Betty Duncan - Social Change in a Metropolitan Community, 1973 (Reel 17)
  - Eaton, Allen and Shelby M. Harrison - A Bibliography of Social Surveys, 1930 (Reel 17)
  - Eaton, Allen H. - Handicrafts of the Southern Highlands, 1937 (Reel 17)
  - Eaton, Allen H. - Immigrant Gifts to American Life, 1932 (Reel 17)
  - Eberly, Donald J. (ed.) - National Service - A Report of a Conference, 1968 (Reel 18)
  - Eiduson, Bernice T. and Linda Beckman (eds.) - Science as a Career Choice, 1973 (Reel 18)
  - Etzioni, Amitai and Richard Remp - Technological Shortcuts to Social Change, 1973 (Reel 19)
  - Feder, Leah Hannah - Unemployment Relief in Periods of Depression, 1936 (Reel 19)
  - Ferriss, Abbot L. - Indicators of Change in the American Family, 1970 (Reel 19)
  - Ferriss, Abbot L. - Indicators of Trends in American Education, 1969 (Reel 19)
  - Ferriss, Abbot L. - Indicators of Trends in the Status of American Women, 1971 (Reel 20)
  - Fledderus, Mary L. and Mary van Kleeck - Technology and Livelihood, 1944 (Reel 20)
  - Folger, John K., Helen S. Astin, and Allan E. Bayer - Human Resources and Higher Education, 1970 (Reel 20)
  - Ford, James - Co-operation in New England, 1913 (Reel 20)
  - Fraenkel, Marta and Carl L. Erhardt - Morbidity in the Municipal Hospitals of the City of New York, 1955 (Reel 21)
  - Frankel, Lee K. and Miles M. Dawson - Workingmen's Insurance in Europe, 1910 (Reel 21)
  - Freidson, Elio - Patients Views of Medical Practice, 1961 (Reel 21)
  - Fremont-Smith, Marion R. - Foundations and Governments, 1965 (Reel 21)
  - Fremont-Smith, Marion R. - Philanthropy and the Business Corporation, 1972 (Reel 22)
  - French, Will - Behavioral Goals of General Education in High School, 1957 (Reel 22)
  - Gallert, David J., Walter S. Hilborn and Geoffrey May - Small Loan Legislation, 1932 (Reel 22)
  - Gardiner, John A. - The Politics of Corruption, 1970 (Reel 22)
  - Glaser, William A. - Pretrial Discovery and the Adversary System, 1968 (Reel 22)
  - Glenn, John M. et al. - Russell Sage Foundation, 1907-1946, Vol. 1, 1947 (Reel 22)
  - Glenn, John M. et al. - Russell Sage Foundation, Vol. 2, 1947 (Reel 23)
  - Glock, Charles W. - Survey Research in the Social Sciences, 1967 (Reel 23)
  - Goldmark, Josephine - Fatigue and Efficiency, Part I and Part II, 1912 (Reel 23)
  - Goodenough, Ward Hunt - Cooperation in Change, 1963 (Reel 24)
  - Goslin, David A. - The Search for Ability, 1963 (Reel 24)
  - Goslin, David A. - Teachers and Testing, 1967 (Reel 25)
  - Goslin, David A. et al. - The Use of Standardized Tests in Elementary Schools, 1965 (Reel 25)
  - Greenblatt, Milton, Richard H. York, and Esther Lucile Brown - From Custodial to Therapeutic Patient Care in Mental Hospitals, 1955 (Reel 25)
  - Greene, M. Louise - Among School Gardens, 1910 (Reel 25)
  - Greenstone, J. David and Paul E. Peterson - Race and Authority in Urban Politics, 1973 (Reel 26)
  - Greenstone, J. David and Paul E. Peterson - Guidelinesfor the Collection, Maintenance, and Dissemination of Pupil Records (Report of a Conference) (Reel 26)
  - Gulick, Lother Halsey and Leonard P. Ayres - Medical Inspection of Schools, 1908 (Reel 26)
  - Gulick, Lother Halsey and Leonard P. Ayres - Medical Inspection of Schools, Revised, 1913, 1913 January (Reel 26)
  - Hall, Fred S. and Elisabeth W. Brooke - American Marriage Laws in their Social Aspects, 1919 (Reel 26)
  - Hamm, John E. - The English Hire-Purchase Act, 1938, 1940 (Reel 26)
  - Harrison, Shelby M. - Attacking on Social Works Three Fronts, 1942 (Reel 26)
  - Harrison, Shelby M. - Social Conditions in an American City, 1920 (Reel 27)
  - Harrison, Shelby M. and F. Emerson Andrews - American Foundations for Social Welfare, 1946 (Reel 27)
  - Harrison, Shelby M. - Public Employment Offices, 1924 (Reel 27)
  - Hart, Hastings H. - Child Welfare in the District of Columbia, 1924 (Reel 27)
  - Hart, Hastings H. - Cottage and Congregate Institutions for Children, 1910 (Reel 28)
  - Hart, Hastings H. - Juvenile Court Laws in the United States, 1910 (Reel 28)
  - Hart, Hastings H. - Plans and Illustrations of Prisons and Reformatories, 1922 (Reel 28)
  - Hart, Hastings H. - Plans for City Police Jails and Village Lockups, 1932 (Reel 28)
  - Hewes, Amy - Women as Munition Makers, 1917 (Reel 28)
  - Walter, Henriette R. - Munition Workes in England and France, 1917 (Reel 28)
  - Hoffman, Martin and Lois Wladis Hoffman - Review of Child Development Research, Vol. I, 1964 (Reel 28)
  - Hoffman, Martin and Lois Wladis Hoffman - Review of Child Development Research, Vol. II, 1966 (Reel 29)
  - Hogg, Margaret H. - The Incidence of Work Shortage, 1932 (Reel 29)
  - Holmen, Milton G. and Richard Docter - Educational and Psychological Testing, 1972 (Reel 29)
  - Hopkirk, Howard W. - Institutions Serving Children, 1944 (Reel 29)
  - Howard, Donald C. - The WPA and Federal Relief Policy, 1943 (Reel 30)
  - Hubachek, F. B. - Annotations of Small Loan Laws, 1938 (Reel 30)
  - Hurlin, Ralph G. and William A. Berridge (eds.) - Employment Statistics for the United States, 1926 (Reel 30)
  - Hurlin, Ralph G. - Operation Statistics of Selected Family Casework Agencies, 1945, 1946 (Reel 31)
  - Hurlin, Ralph G. - Salaries and Qualifications of YWCA Professional Workers (Reel 31)
  - Hurlin, Ralph G. - Scheduled Salariesfor Social Work Positions in Hospitals in New York City, 1946 December; 1947 (Reel 31)
  - Hurlin, Ralph G. - Statistics of Medical Social Casework in New York City, 1945 (Reel 31)
  - Ianni, Francis A. J. and Elizabeth Reuss-Ianni - A Family Business, 1972 (Reel 31)
  - Jaco, E. Gartly - The Social Epidemiology of Mental Disorders, 1960 (Reel 31)
  - Janowitz, Morris - Institution Building in Urban Education, 1969 (Reel 31)
  - Janowitz, Morris - The New Military, 1964 (Reel 31)
  - Johnson, Alexander - The Almshouse, 1911 (Reel 31)
  - Johnson, Earl, Jr. - Justice and Reform, 1974 (Reel 32)
  - Kahn, Alfred J. - Studies in Social Policy and Planning, 1969 (Reel 32)
  - Kahn, Alfred J. - Theory and Practice of Social Planning, 1969 (Reel 32)
  - Katz, Jay - Experimentation with Human Beings, 1972 (Reel 33)
  - Kearney, Nolan C. - Elementary School Objectives, 1953 (Reel 33)
  - Kiger, Joseph C. - Operation Principles of the Larger Foundations, 1954 (Reel 34)
  - King, Stanley H. - Perceptions of Illness and Medical Practice, 1962 (Reel 34)
  - Klein, Alice Campbell - Civil Service in Public Welfare, 1940 (Reel 34)
  - Kein, Philip - The Burden of Unemployment, 1923 (Reel 34)
  - Knutson, Andie L. - The Individual, Society, and Health Behavior, 1965 (Reel 35)
  - Kurtz, Russell H. (ed.) - The Public Assistance Worker, 1938 (Reel 35)
  - Kutner, Bernard et al. - Five Hundred Over Sixty, 1956 (Reel 35)
  - Lavin, David E. - The Prediction of Academic Performance, 1965 (Reel 35)
  - Leichter, Hope Jensen and William E. Mitchell - Kinship and Casework, 1967 (Reel 35)
  - La Dame, Mary - The Filene Store, 1930 (Reel 36)
  - Levy, Harold P. - Building a Popular Movement, 1944 (Reel 37)
  - Levy, Harold P. - A Study in Public Relations, 1943 (Reel 37)
  - Little, Roger W. (ed.) - Selective Service and American Society, 1969 (Reel 37)
  - Lyons, Gene M. - The Uneasy Partnership, 1969 (Reel 37)
  - Macaulay, Stewart - Law and Balance of Power, 1966 (Reel 37)
  - Macgregor, Frances Cooke - Social Science in Nursing, 1960 (Reel 37)
  - May, Geoffrey - Marriage Law and Decisions in the United States, 1929 (Reel 38)
  - Meyer, Henry J. and Edgar F. Borgatta - An Experiment in Mental Patient Rehabilitation, 1959 (Reel 38)
  - Meyer, Henry J. and Wyatt C. Jones - Girls at Vocational High, 1965 (Reel 38)
  - Moore, Wilbert E. - The Professions - Roles and Rules, 1970 (Reel 38)
  - Moskos, Charles C., Jr. - The American Enlisted Man, 1970 (Reel 38)
  - Nelson, Ralph L. - The Investment Policies of Foundations, 1967 (Reel 39)
  - Nesbitt, Florence - Household Management, 1918 (Reel 39)
  - Nonet, Philippe - Administrative Justice, 1969 (Reel 39)
  - Nugent, Rolf - Consumer Credit and Economic Stability, 1939 (Reel 39)
  - Odencrantz. Louise C. - Italian Women in Industry, 1919 (Reel 39)
  - Ohlin, Lloyd E. - Selection for Parole, 1951 (Reel 40)
  - Ohlin, Lloyd E. - Sociology and the Field of Corrections, 1956 (Reel 40)
  - Orchard, Dorothy Johnson and Geoffrey May - Money Lending in Great Britain, 1933 (Reel 40)
  - Paradise, Viola - Toward Public Understanding of Casework, 1948 (Reel 40)
  - Paul, Benjamin D. - Health, Culture and Community, 1955 (Reel 40)
  - Perry, Clarence Arthur - Community Center Activities, 1916 (Reel 40)
  - Perry, Clarence Arthur - Housing for the Machine Age, 1939 (Reel 41)
  - Perry, Clarence Arthur - Wider Use of the School Plant, 1910 (Reel 41)
  - Perry, Clarence Arthur - The Work of the Little Theaters, 1933 (Reel 41)
  - The Pittsburgh Survey Series - Women and the Trades. Elizabeth Beardsley Butler, 1909 (Reel 42)
  - The Pittsburgh Survey Series - Homestead - The Households of a Mill Town. Margaret F. Byingtort, 1910 (Reel 42)
  - The Pittsburgh Survey Series - Work Accidents and the Law. Crystal Eastman, 1910 (Rev. 1916) (Reel 42)
  - The Pittsburgh Survey Series - The Steel Workers. John A. Fitch, 1911 (Reel 42)
  - The Pittsburgh Survey Series - The Pittsburgh District. Paul Underwood Kellogg (Editor), 1914 (Reel 43)
  - The Pittsburgh Survey Series - Wage-Earning Pittsburgh. Paul Underwood Kellogg (Editor), 1914 (Reel 43)
  - Pollack, Otto - Integrating Sociological and Psychoanalytic Concepts, 1956 (Reel 44)
  - Pollack, Otto - Social Science and Psychotherapy for Children, 1952 (Reel 44)
  - Polsky, Howard W. - Cottage Six - The Social System of Delinquent Boys in Residential Ttreatment, 1962 (Reel 44)
  - Ralph, Georgia G. - Elements of Record Keeping for Child-Helping Organizations, 1915 (Reel 44)
  - Reeves, Edith - Care and Education of Crippled Children in the United States, 1914 (Reel 44)
  - Reeves, Edith - Training Schools for Delinquent Girls, 1914 (Reel 45)
  - Reynolds, James Bronson (ed.) - Civic Bibliography for Greater New York, 1911 (Reel 45)
  - Richmond, Mary E. and Fred S. Hall - Child Marriages, 1925 (Reel 45)
  - Richmond, Mary E. - The Long View - Papers and Addresses, 1930 (Reel 45)
  - Richmond, Mary E. and Fred S. Hall - Marriage and the State, 1929 (Reel 46)
  - Richmond, Mary E. - Social Diagnosis, 1917 (Reel 46)
  - Richmond, Mary E. - What Is Social Case Work, 1922 (Reel 46)
  - Riley, Matilda White - An Inventory of Research Finding (Aging and Society, Vol. I) (Reel 46)
  - Riley, Matilda White - Aging and the Professions (Aging and Society, Vol. II) (Reel 47)
  - Riley, Matilda White - A Sociology of Age Stratification (Aging and Society, Vol. III) (Reel 47)
  - Robinson, Louis N. and Rolf Nugent - Regulations of the Small, Loan Business, 1935 (Reel 47)
  - Robinson, Louis N. and Maude E. Stearns - Ten Thousand Small Loans, 1930 (Reel 47)
  - Rosenthal, Douglas E. - Lawyer and Client - Who's in Charge, 1974 (Reel 48)
  - Rosenthal, Douglas E. - Volunteer Attorneys and Legal Servicesfor the Poor - New York's CLO Program, 1971 (Reel 48)
  - Rossi, Alice S. and Ann Calderwood - Academic Women on the Move, 1973 (Reel 48)
  - Routzahn, Mary Swain - The ABC of Exhibit Planning (Survey and Exhibit Series), 1918 (Reel 48)
  - Routzahn, Mary Swain - Traveling Publicity Campaigns (Survey and Exhibit Series), 1920 (Reel 49)
  - Routzahn, Mary Swain - Publicity for Social Work, 1928 (Reel 49)
  - Rushmore, Elsie M. - Social Workers' Guide to the Serial Publications of Representative Social Agencies, 1921 (Reel 49)
  - Ryan, Philip Elwood - Migration and Social Welfare, 1940 (Reel 49)
  - San Francisco Relief Survey, 1913 (Reel 49)
  - Saunders, Lyle - Cultural Difference and Medical Care, 1954 (Reel 50)
  - Sayre, Wallace Stanley - Governing New York City, 1960 (Reel 50)
  - Schwartz, Morris S. - The Nurse and the Mental Patient, 1956 (Reel 50)
  - Scheinburg, Eric F. - Law Training in Continental Europe, 1945 (Reel 51)
  - Scott, Robert A. - The Making of Blind Men, 1969 (Reel 51)
  - Selekman, Ben M. - Employees' Representation in Steel Works, 1925 (Reel 51)
  - Selekman, Ben M. - Postponing Strikes, 1927 (Reel 51)
  - Selekman, Ben M. - Sharing Management with the Workers, 1925 (Reel 51)
  - Selekman, Ben M. - Employees' Representation in Coal Mines, 1925 (Reel 51)
  - Selznick, Philip - Law, Society, and Industrial Justice, 1969 (Reel 52)
  - Sheffield, Ada Eliot - The Social Case History, 1920 (Reel 52)
  - Sheldon, Eleanor Harriet Bernet - Pupils and Schools in New York City, 1965 (Reel 52)
  - Sheldon, Eleanor Harriet Bernet - Indicators of Social Change, 1968 (Reel 52)
  - Shurtleff, Flavel - Carrying out the City Plan, 1914 (Reel 53)
  - Simmons, Leo William - Social Science in Medicine, 1954 (Reel 53)
  - Sibley, Elbridge - The Education of Sociologists in the United States, 1963 (Reel 53)
  - Slingerland, William H. - Child-placing in Families, 1918 (Reel 53)
  - Slingerland, William H. - Child Welfare Work in California, 1916 (Reel 53)
  - Slingerland, William H. - Child Welfare Work in Pennsylvania, 1915 (Reel 53)
  - Smith, Charles P. - Achievement-related Motives in Children, 1969 (Reel 54)
  - Crane, Diane - Social Aspects of the Prolongation of Life (Social Science Frontiers, No. 1), 1969 (Reel 54)
  - Duncan, Otis Dudley - Towards Social Reporting - Next Steps (Social Science Frontiers, No. 2), 1969 (Reel 54)
  - Sorenson, James R. - Social Aspects of Human Genetics (Social Science Frontiers, No. 3), 1971 (Reel 54)
  - Henriot, Peter J. - Political Aspects of Social Indicators - Implications for Research (Social Science Frontiers, No. 4), 1972 (Reel 54)
  - Bauer, Raymond - The Corporate Social Audit (Social Science Frontiers, No. 5), 1972 (Reel 54)
  - Zeisel, John - Sociology and Architectural Design (Social Science Frontiers, No.6), 1975 (Reel 54)
  - Hall, Fred S. (ed.) - Social Work Year Book 1929-1933 (Reel 55)
  - Hall, Fred S. (ed.) - Social Work Year Book 1935-1937 (Reel 56)
  - Hall, Fred S. and Russell H. Kurtz (eds.) - Social Work Year Book 1939-1941 (Reel 57)
  - Kurtz, Russell H. (ed.) - Social Work Year Book 1943-1945 (Reel 58)
  - Kurtz, Russell H. (ed.) - Social Work Year Book 1947-1949 (Reel 59)
  - Solenberger, Alice Willard - One Thousand Homeless Men, 1911 (Reel 60)
  - Spicer, Edward Holland - Human Problems in Technological Change, 1952 (Reel 60)
  - Harrison, Shelby M. - The Springfield Survey, Vol. I, 1918 (Reel 61)
  - Harrison, Shelby M. - The Springfield Survey, Vol. II, 1919 (Reel 61)
  - Harrison, Shelby M. - The Springfield Survey, Vol. III, 1920 (Reel 61)
  - Stapleton, William Vaughan - In Defense of Truth, 1927 (Reel 62)
  - Stewart, Annabel M. - Statistical Procedure of Public Employment Offices, 1933 (Reel 62)
  - Stromberg, Ann Helton - Philanthropic Foundations in Latin America, 1968 (Reel 62)
  - Studt, Eliot - C-unit, 1968 (Reel 62)
  - Suchman, Edward H. - Evaluative Research, 1967 (Reel 62)
  - Suchman, Edward H. - Sociology and the Field of Public Health, 1963 (Reel 62)
  - Sussman, Marion B. - The Family and Inheritance, 1970 (Reel 63)
  - Taylor, Eleanor Kendrick - Public Accountability of Foundations and Charitable Trusts, 1953 (Reel 63)
  - Thomas, Edwin J. (ed.) - In-Service Training and Reduced Workloads, 1960 (Reel 63)
  - Tufts, James H. - Education and Trainingfor Social Work, 1923 (Reel 63)
  - Van de Wall, Willem - Music in Hospitals, 1946 (Reel 63)
  - Van de Wall, Willem - Music in Institutions, 1936 (Reel 63)
  - Van Kleeck, Mary - Artificial Flower Makers, 1913 (Reel 64)
  - Van Kleeck, Mary - Miners and Management, 1934 (Reel 64)
  - Van Kleeck, Mary - A Seasonal lndustry, 1917 (Reel 64)
  - Van Kleeck, Mary - Women in the Bookbinding Trade, 1913 (Reel 64)
  - Van Kleeck, Mary - Working Girls in Evening Schools, 1914 (Reel 64)
  - Veiller, Lawrence - Housing Reform, 1910 (Reel 65)
  - Veiller, Lawrence - A Model Housing Law, 1914 (Reel 65)
  - Veiller, Lawrence - A Model Housing Law, Revised Edition, 1920 (Reel 65)
  - Veiller, Lawrence - A Model Tenement House Law, 1910 (Reel 65)
  - von Mering, Otto - Remotivating the Mental Patient, 1957 (Reel 65)
  - Warfield, George Alfred - Outdoor Relief in Missouri, 1915 (Reel 65)
  - Warren, Roland Leslie - Social Research Consultation, an experiment in health and welfare planning, 1963 (Reel 65)
  - Warren, Roland Leslie - Studying Your Community, 1955 (Reel 66)